Guide to the AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1935-1978; 1962-1976; 0450-003; 62.97 cubic feet 63 boxes
  - WASHINGTON STATE LABOR COUNCIL, OFFICERS AND DIRECTORS RECORDS, SERIES III
    - Education Director, Subseries C
      - Subject Files, Sub-Subseries 6
        - Washington
          - Apprenticeship and Training Council, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 43/17)
          - Central Washington University, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 43/18)
          - Community College Education Board
            - General Correspondence, 1967-1971, Undated (Box-folder 43/19)
            - Minutes and Agenda, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 43/20-43/21)
            - Reports, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 43/22)
            - Newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 43/23)
            - News Releases, 1969-1973, Undated (Box-folder 43/24)
            - Miscellaneous, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 43/25)
          - Eastern Washington State University, 1968 (Box-folder 43/26)
          - Education Board, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 43/27)
          - Evergreen State College, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 44/1)
          - Higher Education Council, 1969 (Box-folder 44/2)
          - Personnel Board, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 44/3)
          - Personnel Department, Salary Survey Findings, 1970 (Box-folder 44/4)
          - Public Instruction Superintendent
            - General Correspondence, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 44/5-44/6)
            - Reports, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 44/7)
            - Miscellaneous, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 44/8)
        - Washington Education Association (W.E.A.), 1964-1968 (Box-folder 44/9)
        - Washington State School Directors' Association, Undated (Box-folder 44/10)
        - Watchdog Project, 1971 (Box-folder 44/11)
      - Central Labor Council Pierce County, Community Services Committee, Adult Education Program Committee
        - General Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 44/12)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 44/13)
        - Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 44/14)
      - Comprehensive Health Planning Council, South Puget Sound (Region 5), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 44/15)
      - 4-H Foundation, Washington State, Board of Trustees
        - General Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 44/16)
        - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 44/17)
      - KPEC - TV, Program Advisory Board
        - General Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 44/18)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 44/19)
        - Clippings, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 44/20)
        - Miscellaneous, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 44/21)
      - Northwest Adult Education Association
        - Organization, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 44/22)
        - General Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 44/23)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 44/24)
        - Financial Records, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 44/25)
        - Conferences and Conventions - Annual, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 44/26)
        - Newsletters - NWAEA Notes, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 44/27)
        - Clippings, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 44/28)
        - Ephemera, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 44/29)
        - Miscellaneous, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 44/30)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor College
        - Organization, 1977 (Box-folder 44/31)
        - General Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 44/32)
        - Mintues and Agenda, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 44/33)
        - Newsletters, 1977 (Box-folder 44/34)
        - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box-folder 44/35)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor History Conference
        - Organization, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 44/36)
        - General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 44/37)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 44/38)
        - Speeches and Writings, 1976, Undated (Box-folder 44/39)
        - Conferences and Conventions
          - General Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 45/1)
          - Ephemera, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 45/2)
          - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 45/3)
        - Notes, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 45/4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 45/5)
      - Public Broadcasting Corporation, Long-Range Financing Task Force
        - General Correspondence, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 45/6)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1973 (Box-folder 45/7)
        - Miscellaneous, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 45/8)
      - Seattle Community College, Board of Trustees, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 45/9)
      - Seattle-King County Adult Education Committee, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 45/10)
      - Washington Corrections Clearing - House Advisory Board
        - Organization, 1975 (Box-folder 45/11)
        - General Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 45/12)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 45/13)
        - Reports, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 45/14)
        - Newsletters - Outside Insight, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 45/15)
        - Subject File- Washington Vocational Education Commission
          Formerly: Washington Occupational Education Coordinating Council.
          - General Correspondence, 1968-1976, Undated (Box-folder 45/16)
          - Minutes and Agenda, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 45/17)
          - Reports, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 45/18)
          - Newsletters, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 45/19)
          - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 45/20)
        - Subject File - Washington Vocational Education Commission, Vocational Rehabilitation Division, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 45/21)
        - Subject File - Washington Vocational Education Commission, Vocational Rehabilitation Division, Sheltered Workshop Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box-folder 45/22)
      - Washington Legislature, Education Committee (Joint), 1969
        - Subject Files
          - Curriculum Subcommittee, 1968 (Box-folder 45/24)
          - Health Services and Education Subcommittee, 1970 (Box-folder 45/25)
          - Higher Education Subcommittee, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 45/26)
          - Indian and Migrant Education Subcommittee, 1970 (Box-folder 45/27)
          - Instruction Subcommittee, 1967 (Box-folder 45/28)
          - Metropolitan Education Subcommittee
            - Minutes and Agenda, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 45/29)
            - Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 45/30)
          - School Finance Subcommittee
            - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 45/31)
            - Minutes and Agenda, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 45/32)
            - Clippings (Box-folder 45/33)
            - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 45/34)
          - School Organization and Management Subcommittee, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 45/35)
      - Washington Legislature, Education Committee (Joint), Occupational, Adult and Institutional Education Subcommittee
        - General Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 45/36)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 45/37)
        - Reports, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 45/38)
        - Testimony, 1968 (Box-folder 45/39)
        - Notes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 45/40)
        - Miscellaneous, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 45/41)
      - Washington Legislature, Education Committee (Joint), Tuition and Fees Subcommittee
        - General Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 46/1)
        - Minutes and Agenda, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 46/2)
        - Legislation, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 46/3)
        - Reports, 1976 (Box-folder 46/4)
        - Notes, 1976 (Box-folder 46/5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box-folder 46/6)
      - Washington Postsecondary Education Council, Financial Aid Task Force
        - General Correspondence and Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 46/7)
        - Reports, 1977 (Box-folder 46/8)
        - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 46/9)
      - Washington Public Instruction Superintendent
        - Career Education Advisory Committee
          - General Correspondence and Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 46/10)
          - Reports, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 46/11)
          - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box-folder 46/12)
        - Educational Personnel Development Study, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 46/13)
        - Manpower Study Committee (Advisory), 1972 (Box-folder 46/14)
        - Professional Education Committee (Advisory)
          - General Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 46/15)
          - Minutes and Agenda, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 46/16)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 46/17)
          - Bulletins, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 46/18)
          - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 46/19)
        - Teacher Education and Certification Committee (Advisory), 1969-1972 (Box-folder 46/20)
        - Urban, Rural, Racial and Disadvantaged Education Program Committee (Advisory)
          - Organization, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 46/22)
          - General Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 46/23)
          - Minutes and Agenda, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 46/24-46/25)
          - Reports, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 46/26)
          - Questionnaries, 1976-1977, Undated (Box-folder 46/27)
          - Grant Proposals, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 46/28)
          - Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 46/29)
      - Washington, State University, Rural Development Council (Advisory), 1973 (Box-folder 46/21)
      - Washington Vocational Rehabilitation Planning Commission, King County Committee (Advisory), 1968-1969 (Box-folder 46/30)
      - Washington Library Association, National Library Week State Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 46/31)
      - Washington Vocational Association, Vocational Education, Vocational Rehabilitation Study Committee (Joint), 1969-1972 (Box-folder 46/32)
      - Washington State Labor Bicentennial Commission -- Subject Files, 1974-1976
        - AFL-CIO Working American Bicentennial Project, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 47/1)
        - American Revolution Bicentennial Administration, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 47/2)
        - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, Washington State, 1974, Undated (Box-folder 47/3)
      - Western Washington Task Force For Drop-Out Rehabilitation, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 47/4)
    - Government Affairs Director, Subseries D
      - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 47/5)
      - Speeches and Writings, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 47/6)
    - Research Director, Subseries E
      - Outgoing Correspondence -- Kenney, Lawrence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 47/7-47/9)
      - General Correspondence, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 47/10)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 47/11-47/14)
      - Reports, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 45/15-47/17)
      - Statements, 1977 (Box-folder 47/18)
      - Newsletters, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 47/19-47/20)
      - Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 47/21)
      - Washington Legislature, Property Tax Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 47/22)
      - Washington Manpower Planning Council, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 47/23-47/24)
      - King-Snohomish Manpower Consortium, King County Employment and Training Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 47/25-47/28)
      - Washington Governor, Employment Development Services Council, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 47/29, 48/1)
      - Justice Under State Taxation, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 48/2-48/3)
      - Washington Full Employment Action Council, 1977 (Box-folder 48/4-48/5)
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF LABOR (AFL), LABOR'S LEAGUE FOR POLITICAL EDUCATION (WASHINGTON) RECORDS, SERIES IV
    - General Correspondence, 1950-1951; Subseries A (Box-folder 48/6-48/8)
    - Reports, 1952-1953; Subseries B (Box-folder 48/9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950; Subseries C (Box-folder 48/10)
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF LABOR - CONGRESS OF INDUSTRIAL ORGANIZATIONS (AFL-CIO, COMMITTEE ON POLITICAL EDUCATION (COPE) (WASHINGTON) RECORDS, SERIES V
    - Organization, 1960; Subseries A (Box-folder 48/11)
    - General Correspondence, 1957-1965; Subseries B (Box-folder 48/12-48/16)
      - With County COPEs, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 48/17-48/18)
      - With WSLC Affiliates, 1946-1964 (Box-folder 48/19-48/20)
      - Requests for Information and Films, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 48/21)
    - Minutes and Agenda, 1960; Subseries C (Box-folder 48/22)
    - Conferences and Conventions, Subseries D
      - COPE Area Conferences, 1961-1972 (Box-folder 48/23-48/32)
      - COPE Statewide Conferences, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 49/1-49/4)
      - COPE District Meetings, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 49/5-49/6)
      - COPE Endorsement Convention, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 49/7-49/14)
      - COPE National Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1973 (Box-folder 49/15)
      - COPE Workshops, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 49/16-49/18)
      - COPE Workshop, #1, Sedro Wooley, February 24, 1968 (Box-folder 49/19)
      - COPE Workshop, #2, Tacoma, March 16, 1968 (Box-folder 49/20)
      - COPE Workshop, #3, Centralia, March 23, 1968 (Box-folder 49/21)
      - COPE Workshop, #4, Seattle, April 6, 1968 (Box-folder 49/22)
      - COPE Workshop, #5, Kennewick, April 13, 1968 (Box-folder 49/23)
      - COPE Workshop, #6, Spokane, April 25, 1968 (Box-folder 49/24)
      - COPE Workshop, #7, Wenatchee, April 27, 1968 (Box-folder 49/25)
    - Financial Records, 1959-1960, 1971; Subseries E (Box-folder 49/26)
    - Newsletters, 1958-1960; Subseries F (Box-folder 49/27)
    - Ephemera, 1972-1976; Subseries G (Box-folder 49/28-49/31)
    - Subject Files, Subseries H
      - Activities Survey, Undated (Box-folder 49/32)
      - Computer Political Addressing Program, National, 1973 (Box-folder 49/33)
      - Grants and Allocations
        - Individual Contributions, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 49/34, 50/1)
        - National COPE Allocations Budget, 1972 (Box-folder 50/2)
        - Special Grant to Spokane Central Labor Council, 1967 (Box-folder 50/3)
      - Central Labor Council, King County, Sample Ballot Procedure, 1972 (Box-folder 50/4)
      - Matching Fund Program
        - General Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 50/5)
        - Financial Records, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/6-50/7)
      - Central Labor Councils
        - Anacortes, 1966 (Box-folder 50/8)
        - Benton-Franklin Counties, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/9)
        - Clark, Skamania and West Klickitat Counties, 1966 (Box-folder 50/10)
        - Grand Coulee, 1966 (Box-folder 50/11)
        - Grays Harbor, 1958-1972 (Box-folder 50/12)
        - East Jefferson County, 1966 (Box-folder 50/13)
        - King County, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 50/14)
        - Kitsap County, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 50/15)
        - Kittitas County, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/16)
        - Lewis County, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/17)
        - Lewiston-Clarkston, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/18)
        - Mason County, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/19)
        - Moses Lake, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/20)
        - North Central Washington, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/21)
        - Pacific County, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/22)
        - Pierce County, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/23)
        - Port Angeles, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/24)
        - Skagit Valley, 1966 (Box-folder 50/25)
        - Snohomish County, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/26)
        - Spokane, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/27)
        - Thurston, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/28)
        - Cowlitz-Wahkiakum, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/29)
        - Walla Walla, Columbia and Garfield Counties, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/30)
        - Whatcom County, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/31)
        - Yakima and E. Klickitat, Undated (Box-folder 50/32)
      - Progress Reports, Central Labor Council COPEs, 1966 (Box-folder 50/33)
      - Voter Registration
        - Clark County Project, 1970 (Box-folder 50/34)
        - Get-Out-The-Vote Drive, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 50/35-50/38)
        - Questionnaires, 1971 (Box-folder 50/39)
        - Registered Voter Participation Charts, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 50/40)
        - Registrar Information, 1967 (Box-folder 50/41)
        - V.O.T.E.R., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 50/42-50/43)
      - Voting Records, State and National, 1947-1960 (Box-folder 51/1)
      - Voting Records, Congressional, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 51/2)
  - WASHINGTON STATE LABOR COUNCIL, COPE WOMEN'S ACTIVITIES DEPARTMENT RECORDS, SERIES VI
    - Organization, 1961; Subseries A (Box-folder 51/3)
    - Outgoing Letters - McDowell, Carrie, 1958-1960; Subseries B (Box-folder 51/4)
    - General Correspondence, 1957-1961; Subseries C (Box-folder 51/5)
    - Reports, 1958-1960; Subseries D (Box-folder 51/6)
    - Conferences and Conventions, Subseries E
      - Iowa WAD Conference, 1st, Cedar Rapids, 1963 (Box-folder 51/7)
    - Subject File - Auxiliaries, 1959-1960; Subseries F (Box-folder 51/8)
  - FEDERATED AMERICAN INSURANCE COMPANY RECORDS, SERIES VII
    - Organization, Subseries A
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1959 (Box-folder 51/9)
      - By-laws, 1964 (Box-folder 51/10)
      - Escrow Agreement, Undated (Box-folder 51/11)
      - Proposed Formation of a Life Insurance Company, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 51/12)
      - Underwriting Management Contract, 1972 (Box-folder 51/13)
    - General Correspondence, 1954-1975; Subseries B (Box-folder 51/14-51/17)
      - Stock owned by Washington State Labor Council, 1956-1974 (Box-folder 51/18)
      - Washington State Bar Association, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 51/19)
      - With Insurance Commissioner, 1969 (Box-folder 51/20)
    - Minutes and Agenda, Subseries C
      - Washington State Labor Council, Executive Board, Excerpts, 1954-1974 (Box-folder 51/21)
    - Financial Records, 1959-1969; Subseries D (Box-folder 51/22)
    - Court Papers - Washington State Labor Council vs. Federated American Insurance Company, 1967-1969; Subseries E (Box-folder 51/23-51/24)
    - Reports, Subseries F
      - General, 1961-1972 (Box-folder 51/25-51/26)
      - Analysis of Federated American Insurance Company, Financial Statements, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 51/27)
    - Annual Meetings, 1973-1976; Subseries G (Box-folder 51/28-51/29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1971; Subseries H (Box-folder 51/30)
    - Subject Files, Subseries I
      - Board of Directors
        - General Correspondence, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 51/31)
        - Miscellaneous (Related Papers), 1961-1969 (Box-folder 52/1)
      - Labor Organization Stockholders, 1958-1970 (Box-folder 52/2)
      - Labor Relations, 1956-1968 (Box-folder 52/3)
      - Proxy Election, 1969 (Box-folder 52/4)
      - Proxy Solicitations, 1967, 1969 (Box-folder 52/5-52/7)
      - Stockholders List, 1969 (Box-folder 52/8)
      - Stock Subscription and Promotion, 1954-1975 (Box-folder 52/9)
      - WSLC Resolution No. 53 Concerning Federated American Insurance Company, 1969 (Box-folder 52/10)
  - UNITED LABOR LOBBY RECORDS, SERIES VIII
    - Lobbyists Registration Statements, 1971-1974; Subseries A (Box-folder 52/12)
    - General Correspondence, 1958-1977; Subseries B (Box-folder 52/13-52/16)
    - Minutes and Agenda, 1958-1975; Subseries C (Box-folder 52/17-52/20)
    - Speeches and Writings -- Statements and Positions, 1969-1974; Subseries D (Box-folder 52/21)
    - Financial Records - Lobbyists' Report of Expenditures, 1970-1975; Subseries E (Box-folder 52/22-52/26)
    - Reports, Subseries F
      - Miscellaneous, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 52/27)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, 1971 (Box-folder 52/28)
      - Labor Looks at the Washington State Legislature, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 52/29)
    - Conferences and Conventions, Subseries G
      - Legislative Workshops, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 52/30)
      - United Labor Lobby Legislative Conference and Banquet, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 53/1-53/5)
    - Newsletters, 1961, 1972-1975; Subseries H (Box-folder 53/6)
    - News Releases, 1963; Subseries I (Box-folder 53/7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1956-1962; Subseries J (Box-folder 53/8-53/9)
    - Subject File - "Hot Line" Program, 1975; Subseries K (Box-folder 53/10)
    - Subject File - The Third House, 1969; Subseries L (Box-folder 53/11)
  - WASHINGTON STATE LABOR COUNCIL, WELFARE AND PENSION SERVICE RECORDS, SERIES IX
    - Organization, 1953-1965, Undated; Subseries A (Box-folder 53/12)
    - General Correspondence, 1953-1963; Subseries B (Box-folder 53/13-53/14)
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1953-1962; Subseries C (Box-folder 53/15)
    - Financial Records, Subseries D
      - Departmental, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 53/16)
      - Alaska Laborers Construction Industry Health and Security Fund, 1955-1963 (Box-folder 53/17)
      - Allied Metal Crafts Security Program, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 53/18)
      - Carpet, Linoleum and Soft Tile Layers' Health and Welfare Trust Fund, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 53/19)
      - Culinary Workers and Bartenders, Local 451, Employers and Employees Security Trust Fund, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 53/20)
      - Glassworkers and Industry Health and Welfare Fund, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 53/21)
      - Hotel, Restaurant and Tavern Employees' Trust Fund of Bellingham and Whatcom County, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 53/22)
      - King County Concrete Products Welfare Fund, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 53/23)
      - Machinists Pension Trust Fund, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 53/24)
      - Masonry Security Plan of Washington, 1953-1962 (Box-folder 53/25)
      - Northwest Ironworkers' Employers' Health and Security Fund, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 53/26)
      - Operating Engineers International Union Locals 302 and 612 Construction Industry Health and Security Fund, 1953-1963 (Box-folder 53/27)
      - Operating Engineers International Union Locals 302 and 612 Employers' Retirement Fund, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 53/28)
      - Plasterers' and Cement Masons' Health and Security Fund, 1955-1962 (Box-folder 53/29)
      - S.T.U. Employers' Life and Disability Fund, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 53/30)
      - Seattle and King County Pharmacists and Retail Drug Store Employees' Retirement Fund, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 53/31)
      - Seattle Lathers' Employers Security Fund, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 53/32)
      - Seattle Plasterers' Employees' Security Fund, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 53/33)
      - Tacoma Lathers' Employers Security Fund, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 53/34)
      - Typographical Union Employer Pension Trust Fund, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 53/35)
      - Washington Office Employees' Security Trust, 1954-1962 (Box-folder 53/36)
      - Western Washington Cement Masons' Security Fund, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 53/37)
      - Western Washington Laborers' Employers Health and Security Program and Retirement Fund, 1953-1963 (Box-folder 53/38)
    - Legal Documents - Agreements, 1954-1963; Subseries E (Box-folder 53/39)
    - Miscellaneous, 1956-1958; Subseries F (Box-folder 53/40)
  - WASHINGTON STATE LABOR COUNCIL, AD HOC COMMITTEE RECORDS, SERIES X
    - Apprenticeship Committee (Interim), 1967-1968; Subseries A (Box-folder 53/41)
    - Building Committee, Vanderveer Building Project, 1970; Subseries B (Box-folder 53/42)
    - Human Rights Committee, Subseries C
      - General Correspondence, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 53/43)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1967-1974, Undated (Box-folder 53/44)
      - Legislation, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 53/45)
      - Clippings, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 53/46)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 53/47)
    - Local Employees Government Collective Bargaining Legislative Committee, Subseries D
      - General Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 54/1)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 54/2)
      - Legislation, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 54/3)
      - Ephemera, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Research, Administrative and Public Information Committee, Location of WSLC Office in Olympia Feasibility Study, Subseries E
      - General Correspondence, 1945-1970 (Box-folder 54/5)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 54/6)
      - Proposals, 1970 (Box-folder 54/7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box-folder 54/8)
    - State Employee AFL-CIO Unions Committee, 1970; Subseries F (Box-folder 54/9)
    - Washington Industrial Safety and Health Act (WISHA) Monitoring Committee, Subseries G
      - General Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 54/10)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1977 (Box-folder 54/11)
      - Reports, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 54/12)
      - Legislation, 1976 (Box-folder 54/13)
      - Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 54/14)